Guide to the Donald W. Baker College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection, 1950- 1969.
Baker, Donald W. College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection
- Baker, Oalfson, Danks and Fincher, 1965 (Box 5d, Folder VPC.00674)
  Description: D.W. Baker, unidentified man, Peter Olafson, A.G. Danks, and M.G. Fincher seated at a banquet in a wallpapered room. Probably an Annual Conference See also VPC.00274 VPC.00294, VPC.00300, VPC.00301, and VPC.00674.
- Group, probably at Annual Conference, 1965 (Box 5d, Folder VPC.00675)
  Description: Group in a wallpapered dining room. Ice machine visible in back. One man standing, others seated. Probably at Annual Conference. See also VPC.00274 VPC.00294, VPC.00300, VPC.00301, and VPC.00674.
- D.W. Baker in cap and gown, ca. 1960s (Box 5d, Folder VPC.00676)
  Description: D.W. Baker in cap and gown, head shot.
- D.W. Baker in cap and gown, ca. 1960s (Box 5d, Folder VPC.00677)
  Description: D.W. Baker in cap and gown, full shot
- Mrs. Batchelder, Mrs. Lowe and unidentified women, 1964 (Box 5d, Folder VPC.00678)
  Description: Candid of Mrs. Batchelder, Mrs. Lowe and an unidentified woman sitting on a sofa. Three other unidentified women are standing behind them. See also VPC.00135
- Dewitt Baker, Ken McEntee and John McCarthy, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00679)
  Description: Dewitt Baker, Ken McEntee and John McCarthy. McEntee is standing. See VPC.00380, VPC.00381, VPC.00441, and VPC.00679-00682 for what appears to be the same event.
- J.D. Wheat and Andy Morse, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00680)
  Description: J.D. Wheat and Andy Morse. See VPC.00380, VPC.00381, VPC.00441, and VPC.00679-00682 for what appears to be the same event.
- Unidentified man and Arnold Hilbert, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00681)
  Description: Unidentified man and Arnold Hilbert. Unidentified man is standing and speaking. See VPC.00380, VPC.00381, VPC.00441, and VPC.00679-00682 for what appears to be the same event.
- Group including Fox, McEntee, and more, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00682)
  Description: Left to right: H.C. Phelps, Guy G. Stevens, Francis Fox, Albert Miller, Dewitt Baker, Ken McEntee, John McCarthy, and Ardell. See VPC.00380, VPC.00381, VPC.00441, and VPC.00679-00682 for what appears to be the same event.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6" x 10", 1 print on paper
- Sign for the Brush and Palette Tavern, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00683)
  Description: Sign for the Brush and Palette Tavern. Probably the sign for location of the event pictured in VPC.00380, VPC.00381, VPC.00441, and VPC.00679-00682.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 10" x 10", 3 prints on paper
- Two unidentified women, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00684)
  Description: Two unidentified women in saddle shoes and skirts. One may be named Baker.
- Unidentified man and woman, 1963 (Box 3 and 5d, Folder VPC.00685)
  Description: Unidentified man and woman examining plants outside Schurman Hall. Same event is pictured in VPC.00345.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9" 3" x 5", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Drs. Stevens and Zellner and unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00686)
  Description: Ansel Kenneth Zellner, class of 1918, and Guy Gross Stevens, Class of 1911, with unidentified man, eating at a table. Unidentified man is cut out of one print. Stevens is holding a cigar.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "7"" x 7"" 8" x 10", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- John Minster, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00687)
  Description: Candid of John Minster, class of 1932
- Dr. DuBois Jenkins and his wife, 1964 (Box 3 and 5d, Folder VPC.00688)
  Description: Candid of Dr. DuBois Jenkins (Class of 1943) and his wife at a Hawaiian dinner party. Dr. Jenkins is wearing a straw hat and his wife is wearing a lei. Same event is pictured in VPC.00689 and VPC.00690.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "7"" x 8.5"" 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Dr. DuBois Jenkins and his wife, 1964 (Box 5d, Folder VPC.00689)
  Description: Dr. DuBois Jenkins and his wife at a Hawaiian dinner party. The doctor is facing away from the camera. Same event is pictured in VPC.00688 and VPC.00690.
- Unidentified woman at a Hawaiian dinner party., 1964 (Box 5d, Folder VPC.00690)
  Description: Unidentified woman at a Hawaiian dinner party. Same event is pictured in VPC.00689 and VPC.00690.
- Erskin Morse (Box 3, Folder VPC.00691)
  Description: Erskin Morse, class of 1944 smoking a cigarette, looking at the camera
- Grant Kaley with unidentified man and woman, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00692)
  Description: Grant Kaley, class of 193, with an unidentified man and woman. Kaley is on the right. Both men are holding a cigarette. Same event is pictured in VPC.00693,
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Dinner party head table, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00693)
  Description: Dinner party head table. Grant Kaley the farthest right. Same event is pictured in VPC.00692.
- Drs Axtell and Milks, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00694)
  Description: H. J. Milks, Class of 1904, and Percy Jay Axtell, Class of 1904, shaking hands.
- Stanley Garrison and unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00695)
  Description: Stanley Garrison, class of 1950 on the right and unidentified man on the left. Garrison is wearing a checked shirt and suspenders. They are outside in front of cars
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 10", 2 prints on cardboard
- Dr. Eugene M. Jones, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00696)
  Description: Candid of Eugene M. Jones class of 1950 from Oklahoma State College of Veterinary Medicine standing outside in front of a large light-colored building.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6.5" x 9", 1 print on paper
- Hugh Mouat and E.J. Magee, 1955 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00697)
  Description: Hugh R. Mouat, Class of 1929, and E.J. Magee. Both are guests at the 47th Annual Conference in 1955.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Donald D. Delahanty, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00698)
  Description: Donald D. Delahanty, class of 1947 looking right in a crowd
  Size and Number of Photographs: 2.5" x 3", 1 print on paper
- Dave Armstrong, 1962 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00699)
  Description: Candid of Dave Armstrong, Class of 1930, wearing a white tuxedo, looking left
- Dave Armstrong and wife, 1962 (Box 3 and 5d, Folder VPC.00700)
  Description: Dave Armstrong, Class of 1930, and his wife. He is wearing a white tuxedo. Both are looking at the camera
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4" x 10", 3" x 5", 2 prints on paper
- Dave Armstrong and wife, dancing, 1962 (Box 5d, Folder VPC.00701)
  Description: Dave Armstrong and wife, dancing.
- A. K. Zellner, 1959 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00702)
  Description: Candid of A. K. Zellner, class of 1918 smoking a cigar, wearing glasses, a hat, and a bow tie.
- Leonard Tyler, 1961 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00703)
  Description: Leonard Tyler holding up 2 kittens standing in front of a blackboard
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Haley, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00704)
  Description: Candid of "Haley" standing behind a desk smiling and holding his glasses.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 7.5", 8" x 10", 5" x 7", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 transparency"
- H.K. Cooper, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00705)
  Description: H.K. Cooper, standing, wearing an Annual Conference name tag and smiling
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6" x 9", 1 print on cardboard
- Dr. and Mrs. George E. Burch, ca. 1950s (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00706)
  Description: Dr. and Mrs. George E Burch, Class of 1936, sitting at a breakfast table with their beagle.
- Annual Conference dinner, 1961 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00707)
  Description: Annual Conference dinner. Same event is pictured in VPC.00080, VPC.00302, and VPC.00707-00710.
- Annual Conference dinner, 1961 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00708)
- Annual Conference dinner, 1961 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00709)
- Annual Conference dinner, 1961 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00710)
- Mrs. Edward Leonard, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00711)
  Description: Candid of Mrs. Edward Leonard, wearing an Annual Conference name tag, with her purse in her lap.
- Katherine Blaisdell, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00712)
  Description: Katherine Blaisdell, wife of Edward Blaisdell, class of 1952, holding 3 kittens
- Drs. Delaney and Corwin, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00713)
  Description: James M. Delaney, Class of 1921, Louis A. Corwin, Class of 1919, and unidentified man. Delaney is in the middle wearing a hat partially askew. They are standing inside the doors of the Concord wearing name badges.
- E. E. Leasure and A. Grothe, 1962 (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00714)
  Description: E. E. Leasure (Kansas State 1923) and A. H. Groth (ISU 193) at the 75th Annual Meeting of the Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 3" x 5", 3 prints on cardboard (2 cropped) 3 prints on paper (2 cropped)"
- Dr. and Mrs. Barber, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00715)
  Description: Dr. and Mrs. Barber standing outside. She is wearing a fur coat. He is holding his coat over his arm.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 10" x 10", 4" x 9", 3 prints on paper (one cropped)
- Peter Kennedy, 1953 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00716)
  Description: A Peter Kennedy collage presented to him at his farewell party. Picture used is VPC.00838.
- Blood and Peter Kennedy, 1960 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00717)
  Description: Candid of Douglas Blood, from Australia and Peter Kennedy. The clock behind them reads 10:07.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 4.5" x 6", 3" x 5", 3 prints on paper (one cropped)
- Dr. Richard Hoey, ca.1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00718)
  Description: Candid of Richard Hoey standing with arms crossed at an Annual Conference
- Alice Purrington Cramer, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00719)
  Description: Alice Purrington Cramer, librarian, seated. She is wearing a corsage and smiling at the camera. See also VPC.00731
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4" x 6", 1 print on paper
- Library Christmas party, 1963 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00720)
  Description: Library Christmas party (left to right): Rozita Chedzoy, Catherine Brown, Rosanna Allen, Anne Mekeel, Patricia Westline, Alison Casserett, Ruth Corman
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5.5" x 9", 2 prints on cardboard
- Drs. Fortune, Fuller and Henderson, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00721)
  Description: Howard K. "Cap" Fuller, class of 1932, giving a demonstration outside. Richard L. Fortune, Class of 1935, and J.A. Henderson, Ontario Class of 1936, are in the background. The demonstration involved eggs.
- Dedication of Savage Hall, 1947 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00722)
  Description: Dedication of Savage Hall, October 15, 1946Governor Dewey--facing camera
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4" x 4.5", 1 print on paper
  Photographer (if other than Baker): John F. Brock - Cornell Photo Science Service
- Clarence Combs, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00723)
  Description: Clarence Combs wearing a plaid tie, holding a hand near his face.
- Procedure Used in Examination of mite Specimens, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00724)
  Description: A photo-essay on the "procedure used in the examination of mite specimens" by D.W. Baker. Includes pictures of him at the microscope.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 8", 2 prints on paper
- Richard Gutherie, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00725)
  Description: Richard Guthrie, class of 1930
  Size and Number of Photographs: 1" x 1", 8.5" x 11" paper, 1 print on paper
- Ellis P. Leonard, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00726)
  Description: Ellis P. Leonard, class of 1934, talking to W. F. Witter, class of 1934. Leonard is wearing saddle shoes and surgery scrubs.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 9" (cropped), 7.5" x 9.5", 1 print on paper 1 print on cardboard
- Dr. Joseph O'Dey, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00727)
  Description: Dr. Joseph O'Dey, veterinarian for the Olympic Games in 1976
- H. S. White, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00728)
  Description: Candid of H. S. White, class of 1942
- Collage, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00729)
  Description: Picture of a collage done for John K Bosshart, Class of 1912?
- Robert E. Habel, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00730)
  Description: Candid of Robert E. Habel with arms crossed, laughing
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4.5" x 8", 1 print on paper
- Alice Purrington, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00731)
  Description: Candid of Alice Purrington, librarian, with an unidentified man. She is smiling and looking away from the camera. She is wearing a corsage. See also VPC.00719.
- President Edmund Ezra Day, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00732)
  Description: Unidentified man and President Edmund Ezra Day
- Julius Fabricant, August 1964 (Box 5d, Folder VPC.00733)
  Description: Candid of Julius Fabricant, wearing a bow tie, shirt sleeves, and glasses. Portrait of fruit behind him.
- L. E. Field, and H. K. Fuller and unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00734)
  Description: Lincoln E. Field (Class of 1930), H. K. Fuller (Class of 1932) and Forbes Bushnell (Class of 1933) sitting down, presumably at a conference (all wearing name tags)
- Dr. Crawford and wife, ca. 1950s (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00735)
  Description: Dr. Crawford and wife and unidentified man in military uniform. Mrs. Crawford is wearing a fur coat.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5.5" x 8", 1 print on paper
- Louise Barr, 1964 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00736)
  Description: Louise Barr receiving flowers
- Joseph B. Engle and daughter Claire, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00737)
  Description: Joseph B. Engle class of 1926 and his daughter Claire. They are standing outside. He's wearing a suit and bow tie. She's wearing a winter coat.
- Dr. Kernkamp, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00738)
  Description: Dr. Kernkamp from University of Minnesota. He has a mustache, glasses, and a bow tie
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9", 1 print on cardboard, 1 transparency
- George Goode's clinic sign, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00739)
  Description: Photo of a sign saying: Geo A. Goode, DVM, Veterinarian, Dog & Cat Hospital
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x7", 1 print on paper
- Unidentified man in the lab, ca. 1950s (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00740)
  Description: Unidentified man in the lab, bending over a specimen tray. He is wearing glasses and a watch.
- Unidentified woman filing, 1962 (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00741)
  Description: Unidentified woman filing, probably a member of the college administrative staff.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 3" x 5", 8" x 10", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Unidentified woman sorting through papers, 1962 (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00742)
  Description: Unidentified woman sorting through papers, probably a member of the college administrative staff.
- Unidentified man on steps of Willard Straight Hall?, ca. 1955 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00743)
  Description: "Unidentified man on steps of Willard Straight Hall? He looks Asian, is wearing a suit, and is holding a camera. A sign in the background read, ""Frosh '55 '54 '53 CLAE NAVY Tickets here"""
- Unidentified man on airplane, 1961 (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00744)
  Description: Unidentified man on airplane. He's holding a cigarette and a mystery book. The cockpit is visible in the background.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 3" x 5", 5" x 7", 2 prints on paper
- Unidentified man on airplane, 1961 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00745)
  Description: Unidentified man on airplane. He's holding a cup and a cigarette.
- 2 unidentified men on an airplane, 1962 (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00746)
  Description: 2 unidentified men on an airplane. The man facing the camera is wearing glasses and a tie but not jacket. The other man is facing away.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 2 prints on cardboard (cropped), 1 print on paper
- Four unidentified people on an airplane, 1962 (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00747)
  Description: Four unidentified people on an airplane, three men and one woman. They are looking at a map. The woman is also pictured in VPC.00114.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 3" x 5", 2 prints on paper
- Unidentified group of six men, 1964 (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00748)
  Description: Unidentified group of six men in suits in an office.. Four are standing and two are sitting.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 3" x 5", 8" x 10", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Morely Kare, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00749)
  Description: Candid of Morely Kare (physiology) and her husband (?) at commencement
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 7.5", 1 print on paper
- Dr. and Mrs. George Christensen (Box 4, Folder VPC.00750)
  Description: Candid of Dr. and Mrs. George Christensen, class of 1951 at commencement
- Walter Sickles and family, 1950 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00751)
  Description: Walter Sickles, class of 1950 and family at graduation
- Daniel Hannigan and Mrs. Hannigan, 1950 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00752)
  Description: Daniel Hannigan, class of 1950 and Mrs. Hannigan at commencement
- Unidentified couple at commencement, ca. 1950 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00753)
  Description: Unidentified couple at commencement
- Unidentified couple at commencement, ca. 1950 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00754)
- Three unidentified people at commencement, ca. 1950 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00755)
  Description: Three unidentified people at commencement, two men and a woman.
- Unidentified graduate and family at commencement, ca. 1950 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00756)
  Description: Unidentified graduate and family at commencement
- Unidentified graduate and older man at commencement, ca. 1950 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00757)
  Description: Unidentified graduate and older man at commencement
- 2 unidentified graduates at commencement, ca. 1950 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00758)
  Description: 2 unidentified graduates at commencement
- Unidentified graduate at commencement, ca. 1950 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00759)
  Description: Unidentified graduate at commencement standing in front of parked cars
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6" x 7", 7" x 9", 2 prints on paper
- Unidentified graduate at commencement, ca. 1950 (Box 4, Folder VPC.00760)
  Description: Unidentified graduate at commencement
- Student group in Autopsy, 1962 (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00761)
  Description: Students performing an autopsy on a cow
- Side door of the old James Law, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00762)
  Description: Front view of the side door of the old James Law building
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 11", 1 print on cardboard
- Schurman Hall, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00763)
  Description: View of Schurman Hall--Veterinary Medicine "Headquarters-CORNELL AGRICULTURAL PROGRESS DAYS--information center
- Moore Laboratory Front Entrance, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00764)
  Description: Front entrance of Moore Laboratory. 2 cars are parked out front
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 10", 1 print on paper
- Schurman Hall, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00765)
  Description: Close-view of Schurman Hall--Veterinary Medicine. A dark car is parked out front
- James Law Auditorium and Schurman Hall, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00766)
  Description: James Law and Schurman Hall, taken from the courtyard. Students milling around with exhibits set up. One picture is taken from further away
- James Law Auditorium and Schurman Hall, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00767)
- Door to James Law Hall, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00768)
  Description: Picture of 2 doors leading to James Law Hall. It is covered in ivy.
  Size and Number of Photographs: paper is 8" x 10", picture is 2.5" x 3", 1 print on paper
- Christmas Card (Box 4, Folder VPC.00769)
  Description: A Christmas card with a view of campus with Seasons Greetings, Donald Baker written on it.--James Law, Medicine Building, Moore Laboratory
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4" x 9.5", 2 prints on paper
- Arthur North and three unidentified men, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00770)
  Description: Arthur North and three unidentified men. All four are sitting. Caption on back or original print says one of them is a "visitor from England." Print discarded because of severe curling and tearing
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 1 transparency
- Unidentified Man, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00771)
  Description: Unidentified man standing facing the right, crossing his arms. He has a belt buckle with a "B" on it.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "5"" x 9.5"" 4" x 8.5", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Unidentified man pouring grain, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00772)
  Description: Unidentified man pouring grain out of a bucket.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 10" x 10", 9.5" x 11", 2 prints on paper
- Unidentified man with cow, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00773)
  Description: Unidentified man inspecting cow's mouth with a flashlight
  Size and Number of Photographs: 10.5" x 9", 1 print on cardboard
- Unidentified man with suitcase, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00774)
  Description: Unidentified man with suitcase at airport
- Unidentified Faculty member at Annual Conference, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00775)
  Description: Unidentified Faculty member at Annual Conference looking to his right smiling with his arms crossed
- 2 unidentified men, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00776)
  Description: 2 unidentified men. One older who is pursing his lips. The other is wearing a suit and a hat
  Size and Number of Photographs: 10" x 10" and 7.5" x 8", 2 prints on paper
- Unidentified Black man using microscope, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00777)
  Description: Unidentified Black student or doctor at microscope.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 7.5" x 9.5", "2 prints on paper 1 print on cardboard
- Unidentified Man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00778)
  Description: An unidentified man smiling and blinking. Wearing a suit with an overcoat in front of a brick wall
- Unidentified man inspecting a cow, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00779)
  Description: Unidentified man inspecting a cow. Same man is pictured in VPC.00794
- Unidentified Man, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00780)
  Description: Unidentified man holding a piece of bread. He has circle glasses and a suit on
- A bride and possibly the father of the bride, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00781)
  Description: Unidentified bride and father-of the bride (?) See also VPC.00419
- Unidentified man and woman, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00782)
  Description: Unidentified man and woman. The man is looking right, woman looking into camera. She is wearing a velvet dress and netting in her hair.
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00783)
  Description: "Unidentified man, holding a card and a pen, talking to another man. Caption on back reads, "" Pritchard?
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 3 prints on cardboard (cropped), 1 print on paper
- 3 unidentified students, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00784)
  Description: 3 unidentified students, probably an Honor Day group. See also VPC.00524.
- Unidentified woman, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00785)
  Description: Unidentified woman standing in front of blinds, holding a piece of paper. Possibly a secretary.
- Unidentified man, 1964 (Box 4 and 5d, Folder VPC.00786)
  Description: Unidentified man holding a dog by its head and tail
- Unidentified woman, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00787)
  Description: Unidentified woman. She had her hands crossed in front over the back of a chair and is exposing the right side of her neck
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 7", 1 print on paper
- Unidentified man in front of a car, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder VPC.00788)
  Description: Unidentified man standing behind an open car door
- Unidentified man (Box 4, Folder VPC.00789)